Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/wolfgang-rebhan-a70ba7165 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Customer Service

Customer Experience

Customer Relationship Management (CRM)

Certifications

ServiceNow Certified Systems Administrator

Wolfgang Rebhan

Sr Staff Support Account Manager at ServiceNow Knoxville, Tennessee, United States

Summary

Personable, accomplished Customer Success Manager highly regarded for a proven track record of enhancing the customer experience through understanding, specialized support, and acute product and service knowledge at Veritas Technologies LLC. Outof-the-box, analytical thinker who pushes creative limits to solve political and technical issues, optimizing project outcomes and customer satisfaction. Recognized for performing research, analysis, and data management to track customer trends and improve retention. Seen as a self-starter with excellent oral and written communication skills, and as a team player able to work with people at all levels of a corporation.

Experience

ServiceNow

4 years

Sr Staff Support Account Manager March 2022 - Present (1 year 9 months)

Knoxville, Tennessee, United States

Sr Staff Support Account Mgr March 2022 - Present (1 year 9 months)

Remote

Support Account Manager
December 2019 - Present (4 years)

Orlando, Florida Area

Proofpoint

Archiving and Information Governance Sr. Technical Account Manager May 2019 - December 2019 (8 months)

Archiving and Information Governance specialist

Veritas Technologies LLC 16 years 10 months

Customer Success Manager October 2015 - May 2019 (3 years 8 months)

Heathrow, FI

- # Deliver rapid, onsite response to catastrophic break-fix issues and proactive, preventative maintenance to financial and government customers, and an American multinational courier delivery service, with 2,000 to 100,000 end users.
- # Aid in resolving high-profile cases with business-critical customers and play a key role in expediting resolutions.
- # Identify data inconsistencies within databases and determine the appropriate action plan to resolve complex issues.
- # Collaborate with the account manager in troubleshooting specific issues and escalating to engineering to expedite.
- # Develop and deliver customer-facing technical webinars with up to 100 attendees and answer any questions.
- # Create and provide presentations highlighting new features in upcoming product builds or discussing customer pain points with Enterprise Vault, accentuating the use of best practice skills to reduce support cases.
- # Guide customers through planning and delivery of onsite and remote upgrades for very complex scenarios and follow up with the customer after the upgrade process to ensure customer satisfaction.
- # Provide an environmental health check review service to deliver the most stable environment possible and ensure the customer is following best practice strategies.
- # Aid customer with disaster recovery planning to provide data restoration in the event of data loss, and with upgrading databases and server environments to maintain product compatibility requirements.
- # Participate in customer roundtable discussions to answer questions and concerns about products and performance.

Customer Service Advisor August 2002 - May 2019 (16 years 10 months) heathrow, fl

Technical Support Engineer for Backup Exec and Enterprise Vault August 2002 - July 2003 (1 year)

Heathrow, FI

Enhanced customer experiences with company products and increased customer service ratings.

Played a key role in resolving case-related issues in a timely manner to enhance customer satisfaction.

Guided customers in disaster recovery scenarios and aided them in recovering data quickly.

Symantec

12 years 4 months

Customer Success Manager August 2007 - October 2015 (8 years 3 months) Heathrow, FI

Deliver rapid, onsite response to catastrophic break-fix issues and proactive, preventative maintenance to financial and government customers, and an American multinational courier delivery service, with 2,000 to 100,000 end users.

Aid in resolving high-profile cases with business-critical customers and play a key role in expediting resolutions.

Identify data inconsistencies within databases and determine the appropriate action plan to resolve complex issues.

Collaborate with the account manager in troubleshooting specific issues and escalating to engineering to expedite.

Develop and deliver customer-facing technical webinars with up to 100 attendees and answer any questions.

Create and provide presentations highlighting new features in upcoming product builds or discussing customer pain points with Enterprise Vault, accentuating the use of best practice skills to reduce support cases.

Guide customers through planning and delivery of onsite and remote upgrades for very complex scenarios and follow up with the customer after the upgrade process to ensure customer satisfaction.

Provide an environmental health check review service to deliver the most stable environment possible and ensure the customer is following best practice strategies.

Aid customer with disaster recovery planning to provide data restoration in the event of data loss, and with upgrading databases and server environments to maintain product compatibility requirements.

Participate in customer roundtable discussions to answer questions and concerns about products and performance.

Technical Support Engineer for Enterprise Vault July 2003 - August 2007 (4 years 2 months)

Heathrow, FI

Enhanced customer experiences with company products and increased customer service ratings.

Played a key role in resolving case-related issues in a timely manner to enhance customer satisfaction.

Guided customers in disaster recovery scenarios and aided them in recovering data quickly.

Education

University of Phoenix MCSE Certification, MCSE · (1996 - 1997)